老爸老妈罗曼史\n第一季 第十九集
How.I.Met.Your.Mother\nSeason 1 Episode 19
[三个月前]\n你们知道她最喜欢Otis Redding\n合集中的哪张CD吗?
[three month earlier]\nHer favorite CD in the Otis Redding box set?
第三碟
Disc three.
我最喜欢的呢?
My favorite?
有人能猜到吗?有人吗? 加油
Any guesses? Anyone? Come on.
第三碟!
Disc three!
天,Victoria太棒了! 我可以几个小时都说她
God,Victoria's so amazing! I could talk about her for hours.
你说“可以”是什么意思?
What do you mean "could"?
对不起 只是... 天,我... 我很为这个女孩着迷
I'm sorry,it's just... God,I... I'm crazy about this girl.
我觉得也许... 我不想这么说
It feels like maybe... I don't want to say it.
相信这种冲动,Ted
Trust that impulse,Ted.
嘿 刚发生了件很酷的事情
Hey. Something kinda cool just happened.
我的小菜故事 - 狗狗唱歌
My story on Pickles - the Singing Dog
刚得到了本地年度传媒奖的题名
just got nominated for a Local Area Media Award.
一个LAME-A题名（本地年度传媒奖缩写）?
a LAME-A?
我们更喜欢叫它“本地年度传媒奖”
We prefer Local Area Media Award.
嗯... 会举行一个大型宴会
Um... there's going to be this big banquet.
我知道这事不是很有意思,但是如果你们能来对我来说是很重要的
I know these things aren't much fun,but it would really mean a lot to me if you guys came.
而且有开放的酒吧
And there's an open bar.
- 好! \n- 说定了!
- Yes! \n- Word up!
好，我要两个人的位子
Yeah,put me down for two.
真的吗? 还有三个月呢
Really? It's three months away.
我知道,但是... 伙计们,抱歉,我要说
I know,but... guys,I'm sorry,I'm going to say it.
我有种感觉  ,Victoria会长时间在我们身边的
I have a feeling Victoria's going to be around for a long time.
三个月后
three months later
我会想Victoria
I'm gonna miss Victoria.
我就别去了 ,Robin还在生我的气... 你们知道
I should just skip this thing entirely. Robin's still pissed at me after... you know.
你说谎和Victoria分手了其实还没有\n因为你想上Robin 却一夜伤了两个女孩的心\n同时失去了她们?
You lied and said you were broken up with Victoria before you actually were so you could try to nail Robin and you wound up losing both girls in one night?
对 ,我说“你们知道”是这个意思
Yes,that's what I meant by "you know."
我三个星期都没见她了 ,她也不回我电话
I haven't seen her in three weeks. She won't return my calls.
瞧 ,我不该去
Look,I shouldn't go.
你绝对应该去
You should definitely go.
瞧 这是表明你还是她的朋友而且你支持她的机会
Look,it's a chance to show her you're still friends and that you support her.
或者你可以带个更漂亮的女朋友去让她难受
Or it's a chance to mess with her head by showing up with someone hotter.
还能更棒，三重威胁：更漂亮、胸部更大
Even better,triple threat: hotter and bigger boobs.
- 这才两个 \n- 再数一遍
- That's only two. \n- Count again.
Barney我不会带女朋友的,就算我愿意,现在也只剩下两小时了
Barney,I'm not bringing a date. Even if I wanted to,the thing's in two hours.
那么找个“伴儿”啊
So get an escort.
你说的“伴儿”是妓女的意思?
By "escort" you mean prostitute?
为什么不呢?
Why not?
因为......不雅?
Because... gross?
哦,不雅,怎么，你对卖淫有道德障碍?
Oh,gross. What,you have some puritanical hang-up about prostitution?
伙计 这是世界上最古老的职业
Dude,it's the world's oldest profession.
你真认为这是事实?
You really think that's true?
哦 是的 ,我打赌甚至Cro-Magnons也找妓女,和鱼一起卖
Oh,yeah. I bet even Cro-Magnons used to give cave hookers, like,an extra fish for putting out.
啊哈,那最古老的职业应该是渔夫
Aha,so then the oldest profession would be fishermen.
Kaboom! 我是律师
Kaboom! You've been lawyered.
来吧,Ted我们给你找个妓女,会很有意思的
Come on,Ted,let's get you a hooker. It'll be fun.
带她去宴会，讽刺的和她装成一对,还是真的和她上床?
Okay,to bring to the banquet and hang out with ironically or to actually have sex with?
对
Yes.
不，这是非法的,而且我有提过这不雅吗?
No! It's illegal. And did I mention gross?
好可爱,Ted你真是个乡下佬
That's adorable. Ted, you're such a hayseed.
色情业是20世纪最成熟的工业
The companionship business is the growth industry of the 21st century.
你要知道每八个成年美国女人中就有一个是妓女
You do realize that one out of every eight adult women in America is a prostitute.
- 你自己编的 \n- 撤销
- You just made that up. \n- Withdrawn.
我是律师
Lawyered.
关键是 你有多久没做爱了?
The point is,how long has it been?
57天
57 days.
- 这是你的水吗? 我可以……? \n- 嗯，喝吧
- Is that your water? May I? \n- Yeah,go ahead.
57天?!
57 days?!
Ted,你阳痿.
Ted,you are in a slump.
不，我没有阳痿
No,it's not a slump.
这是有意识的摆脱女孩
It's an intentional hiatus from girls.
阳痿的人一接近目标就退却了
A slump is when you strike out every time you step up to the plate.
但我不在花名册上,宝贝
But I'm off the roster,baby.
我在更衣室里,坐在混乱中
I'm in the locker room sitting in the whirlpool.
而且我告诉你 这感觉棒极了
And I'll tell you something,it feels pretty good.
对，你知道那间更衣室还有什么吗?
Yeah,you know what else is in that locker room?
一群悬着脑袋的裸体男人
A bunch of naked dudes hanging brain.
Ted,你需要一个女人
Ted,you need a lady.
而且我有个约会的好人选-- Mary
And I've got the next best thing-- Mary.
她住在我那幢楼里
She lives in my building.
她漂亮聪明而且非常酷
She's smart,she's hot,she's totally cool.
哦 她听起来不错
Oh,she sounds great.
谁知道呢,也许有一天我们能结婚
And who knows? Maybe we'll wind up getting married someday.
你知道，如果能得到给她拉皮条老兄的祝福的话
You know,if we can get a blessing from her pimp.
你想只凭一个人的表面的特征去判断他?
You want to judge a fellow human being based solely on one external characteristic?
那是歧视.
That's racism.
而我不会搞歧视的人一起喝酒
And I do not drink with racists.
祝你一天愉快
Good day.
你只是等有人开口 你就可以...
You're just waiting for me to speak,so you can...
我说了祝你一天愉快!
I said good day!
我应该把头发扎起来还是放下来?
So should I wear my hair up or down?
Lily.\nLily.
什么?
What?
- 你怎么了? \n- 哦 没事 对不起
- You okay? \n- Oh,yeah,sorry.
我只是工作太累了
I'm just exhausted from work.
愚蠢的校董会取消了我们幼儿园孩子午睡的时间
The stupid school board took away nap time in all kindergarten classes
现在一天过完的时候孩子们都疯了
and now the kids are just going crazy by the end of the day.
而且因为我也不能午睡了,所以处理起来更难了
It's much harder to deal with because,well,I don't get my nap.
等等，你是说孩子们睡觉的时候你也睡?
Wait,you were taking naps when the kids were?
这安全吗?
Is that safe?
他们才五岁,能对我做什么?
Well,they're only five. What are they gonna do to me?
Ted还是会去,对吗?
Ted's still coming to this thing,right?
对
Yep.
你认为,嗯...假设我带个男人去会奇怪吗?
Do  you think,um... hypothetically... it would be weird if I bring a date?
瞧瞧你 ,Scherbotsky,显然想让Ted忌妒
Look at you,Scherbotsky,blatantly trying to make Ted jealous.
不 只是台里的一个人
No,it's just this guy at the station.
我从不和同事交往,是他问了我,我同意了会奇怪吗
I never get involved with co-workers,but he asked me and I said yes.
会奇怪吗?
Is it going to be weird?
不 一点也不会奇怪
No,it's not going to be weird at all.
Robin要带男人去
Robin's bringing a date.
天啊，会很奇怪的
Boy. That's going to be really weird.
我知道
I know.
Robin要带男人去
Robin's bringing a date.
哦 好啊 不奇怪
Oh. Okay. That's not weird.
她带男朋友.我很高兴她重新开始了
She's bringing a date. I'm glad she's moving on.
- 伙计,会很奇怪的 \n- 不,没关系
- Dude,it's going to be weird. \n- No,it's fine.
瞧，不管我们之间发生了什么,Robin和我还是朋友
Look,in spite of whatever happened between us,Robin and I are still friends.
我不认为会奇怪
I don't think it'll be weird.
- 对 不会奇怪的\n- 谢谢
- Yeah,it won't be weird. \n- Thank you.
因为你也要带女朋友
Because you're going to bring your own date.
- 你好,Barney.\n- 嗨,Mary.
- Hello,Barney. \n- Hi,Mary.
你见过Ted吗?
Have you met Ted?
很高兴认识你Ted
Nice to meet you Ted.
嗨,Mary.
Hi,Mary.
哇 我也很高兴认识你
Wow. It's,uh,nice to meet you,too.
那么我们去颁奖礼吗?
So we're going to an award show?
嗯,对,请原谅 等一等?
Uh,yeah,will you just excuse us for one minute?
Barney.\nBarney.
一会见,Mare
See you in two shakes,Mare.
你们俩随便玩
You two make yourselves comfortable.
见鬼 怎么回事?
What the hell?
伙计，你对色情行业狭窄的观点让我很气愤
Dude,your narrow-minded views on professional fornicators were harshing my mellow.
所以我给你的晚上找了个伴
So I got you a date for the evening.
你给我找了个妓女
You got me a hooker.
- 一个非常漂亮的. \n- 一个妓女!
- A really hot hook.  \n- A hooker!
想想吧 这很完美
Think about it,this is perfect.
A:你能让Robin忌妒到疯掉...
A:it will make Robin insanely jealous...
B:你可以和她上床...
B:ou get to have sex with her...
C:也许你能进一步了解Marry.
and C:maybe by getting to know Mary,
认识到妓女也是人.
you'll come to see that courtesans are people,too.
D:你可以做B整夜.
And D: "B" all night long.
我不会带妓女去Robin的宴会的.
I'm not taking a prostitute to Robin's banquet.
只有我、你和Marshell知道.
The only people who will know are you,me and Marshall.
没人会怀疑
No one will suspect a thing.
他们只会看见你和这一位不可思议的漂亮女孩...
They'll just see you with this unbelievably smoking hot girl and...
哦 好吧 这是有点可疑.
Okay,that's a little bit suspicious.
瞧，我只是想在今晚扩展一下你的界线
Look,I'm just trying to expand your horizons a little bit tonight.
但如果你没兴趣,没关系,我只是浪费了500美元,没什么
But if you're not interested,fine,I'm out 500 bucks. Whatever.
500美元?
500 bucks?
Ted你是我兄弟
Ted,you're my cabron.
你以为我会在港务局给你找个没牙的吗?
You think I'm gonna stick you with some toothless tranny from the Port Authority?
瞧瞧她多辣.Robin会忌妒死的.
Look at how hot she is. Robin would be so jealous.
我不是想让Robin忌妒,Barney.
I'm not trying to make Robin jealous,Barney.
瞧,我... 告诉Marry谢谢,但是不用了,谢谢,我是有灵魂的人
Look,I... tell Mary,thanks. but no thanks. I have a soul.
然后我和Marshell叔叔开始了一段我们最有名的心电交流
And then your Uncle Marhsall and I had one of our famous telepathic conversations.
瞧Robin的男朋友
Check out Robin's date.
我知道
I know.
是我想的那个人吗?
Is that who I think it is?
对
Yep.
是Sandy Rivers
It's Sandy Rivers.
Sandy Rivers是Metro News一台的主持人
Sandy Rivers was the face of Metro News One,
这是有史以来最低成本的失败电视台
the most low-budget cable news network ever.
Sandy时间.Sandy时间!
Sandy time. Sandy time!
他最有名的是早上的读报节目“今日报刊”
He was best known for his morning segment "In Today's Paper,"
他把当天的报纸找来逐字逐句的
during which he literally flipped through today's papers,
给观众读一遍
reading them aloud to viewers.
今天的头版是一个...
Here we have,on the front page,a story about a...
我猜,穿着超级英雄衣服的人爬上了帝国大厦
I guess,a guy in a superhero costume climbing the Empire State Building.
看起来挺有意思
Looks interesting.
这是我们惭愧的一点白痴填充小游戏
These idiotic filler pieces were a guilty pleasure of ours.
我们今天想看什么Sandy?
Which Sandy do we want today?
法国Sandy 艳星Sand...?
French Sandy,porn star Sandy...?
Yosemite Sandy,绝对
Yosemite Sandy,definitely.
选的绝了
Excellent choice.
我爱这人
I love this guy.
我恨这人
I hate this guy.
嘿
Hey.
- 嗨. \n- 我是Lily.
- Hi. \n- I'm Lily.
我是Marry 很高兴见到你
I'm Mary. It's nice to meet you.
Marry是Barney的朋友 Barney邀请了她
Mary is a friend of Barney's. Barney invited her.
只要记住Marry本人,不要了解她太多
Just met Mary ourselves. Don't know too much about Mary.
瞧 啤酒
Look,a beer.
嗨
Hey.
Hi.
- 你看起来很漂亮 \n- 哦，嗯，Ted，这是Sandy
- You look nice. \n- Oh,um,Ted,this is Sandy.
嗨.Sandy Rivers.用我的全名 能让人激动
Hi.Sandy Rivers.Use my full name.People get a kick out of it.
嗨,Sandy...
Hi,Sandy...
Rivers\nRivers.
这么说，你们俩...
So are you two,uh...
在办公室有很多绯闻?
Starting a bunch of office rumors?
好像有哦 好像有哦
Looks that way. Looks that way.
哦 我真没礼貌
Oh,how rude of me.
恩,Robin,Sandy... Rivers...
Uh,Robin,Sandy... Rivers...
这是Marry 我的女朋友
this is Mary,my date.
女士们先生们,欢迎来到第45届本地年度传媒奖颁奖典礼
Ladies and gentlemen,welcome to the 45th annual Local Area Media Awards.
欢迎我们今晚的主持人
Please say hello to our host for the evening,
星期六下午功夫片国王
king of the Saturday Afternoon Kung Fu Movie,
吸血鬼lou!
Vampire Lou!
今晚我将为传播领域最杰出的人物，
Tonight we celebrate the very best in broadcasting
为人类心灵的胜利而庆祝
and the triumph of the human spirit.
伙计，吸血鬼lou真是太棒了
Man,Vampire Lou just looks great.
我不敢相信我在和妓女约会
I can't believe I'm on a date with a hooker.
对，我不敢相信你让她和lily一起去了洗手间，伙计
Yeah,I can't believe you let her and Lily go to the ladies' room together,man.
她们会在那说自己的秘密的
Secrets come out in there.
哦 拜托 怎么说秘密呢?
Oh,please. How's it's going to come out?
"嗯,递给我一条毛巾,顺便说下 我和人上床挣钱"
"Uh,pass me a towel. P.S.,I have sex for money."
- 谁和人上床挣钱? \n- 没有人
- Who has sex for money? \n- Nobody.
你们在那谈了什么,有什么有趣的吗
What did you guys talk about in there? Anything interesting?
不，没什么
No,not really.
我们只是闲谈几句,我向她借了唇膏
We just chitchatted and I borrowed her lipstick.
为什么吸血鬼lou会是星期六下午功夫片的主持人?
Why is Vampire Lou the host of a Saturday Afternoon Kung Fu Movie?
这一点道理都没有
You know,it just makes no sense.
天 气死我了
God,that pisses me off.
lily你还好吗?
Lily,you okay?
哦，没事，我只是累了,我累的时候就变的不正常
Oh,yeah,I'm just tired. And when I get tired,I get cranky.
真的？我可以想象你不正常的样子
Really? I couldn't imagine you cranky.
"真的？我可以想象你不正常的样子"
"Really? I couldn't imagine you cranky."
哇 为什么你这么累?
Wow. Why are you so tired?
我是幼稚园老师,校董会取消了我的午睡时间――孩子们的午睡时间
Well,I teach kindergarten and the school board took away my nap time,the kids' nap time.
lily 别干了
Lily,quit your job.
去个私人学校工作,不用管校董会
Work at a private school. You won't have to deal with the school board,
而且你能挣更多钱
and you'll make a ton more money.
知道吗 Barney ?
Well,guess what,Barney?
我做人生重要决定时并不是根据挣钱的多少
I don't base all my life decisions on how much money I'm going to make,
不像你 可悲的是 也不像我的未婚夫
unlike you and,sadly,my fiance.
我只是在实习，积累经验
Well,it's just an internship,for the record.
因为如果我为了钱而牺牲所以的价值观
Yeah,because if I did sacrifice all my values just for an easy buck,
那我变成什么人了?
what would that make me?
妓女
A prostitute.
完全正确 谢谢 Mary
Exactly. Thank you,Mary.
那么，Mary你是做什么的?
So,Mary,what do you do for a living?
她是个助理律师
She's a paralegal.
对，我是个助理律师
Yes,I'm a paralegal.
哦，那么Mary是助理律师，
Oh,so,Mary the paralegal.
助理律师究竟要做些什么呢?
What does a paralegal do exactly?
我在市区的一家法律公司协助做一些日常行政工作
I just assist with day-to-day clerical work in a law firm downtown.
哦，哪间公司?
Oh,what firm?
Douglas,O'Halloran和Stamp
Douglas,O'Halloran and Stamp.
那是一间真的法律公司
That's a real law firm.
我知道
I know.
棒
Nice.
干得不错
You're pretty good on your feet.
你是在和我调情吗?
Are you flirting with me?
允许吗?
Is that allowed?
对，而且值得鼓励
Yes,it's encouraged.
你知道 我一般初次约会不会这么说...
You know,I wouldn't normally say this on a first date,but...
但是考虑到……
well,considering...
我就说了 你真辣!
I'm just going to say it. You are so hot!
- 谢谢 \n- 不客气
- Well,thank you. \n- You're welcome.
Mary，Ted是个好男人 你一定要看紧他
Mary,Ted is a great guy. You hold on to him.
一分钟也别让他离开你的视线
Don't let him out of your sight for a minute.
那么，Sandy你是做什么的?
So,Sandy,what do you do?
哦，等等 我知道了
Oh,wait,I know what you do.
你是早上读报纸的人
You're the guy who reads the paper in the morning.
你说中了
You got me.
你是做什么的Ted?
What do you do,Ted?
和你一样，我每天早上读报纸
Oh,same thing as you,I read the paper every morning.
但是读完以后 我喝了咖啡就去做我真实的工作了 我是建筑师
But then after that,I finish my coffee and I go to my real job as an architect
我对世界有实际的贡献
where I make an actual contribution to the world.
只是开个玩笑 我喜欢你的节目 你太棒了
I'm just kidding. Love your show. You're terrific.
谢谢
Thanks.
这句话我从来听不腻
I never tire of hearing that.
嘿，你知道帝国时代Darth Vader头上戴着头盔的样子吗?
Hey,you know that scene in Empire where they lower the helmet onto Darth Vader's head?
早上Sandy就是那样，觉得吗?
Do you think that's how Sandy puts his hair on in the morning?
你刚侮辱了我讨厌的人 而且用了我喜欢的方法
You just insulted someone I hate by referencing something I love.
见鬼 你变得更辣了
Damn,you just got even hotter.
那晚后来我逐渐意识到
And so,as the night wore on,I started to realize,
这个女孩，尽管是个妓女，但确实很棒
this girl,despite what she did for a living,was kind of great.
- 嘿 \n- 嘿
- Hey. \n- Hey.
Mary看起来不错
Mary seems nice.
你吻过她了吗？
Have you kissed her yet
还是要等到你和别人发展成为正式的情侣关系以后?
or are you waiting until you're in a serious relationship with someone else?
我，嗯...我要为发生的一切道歉
I,uh... I wanted to apologize for everything that happened.
- 就这样 \n- 我们就没事了
- And just like that,\n- it's all okay.
滚动信用
Roll credits.
那么你要永远生气下去吗?我们现在不是朋友了吗?
So you're going to be mad at me forever? What,we're not even friends now?
- 我们还是朋友 \n- 是吗?
- We're still friends. \n- Are we?
你不回我电话 我们不一起玩了
You don't return my calls,we never hang out
现在你想让我忌妒 就带一个白痴出现在我面前?
and now you're trying to make my jealous by waving Edward R. Moron in my face?
哦，你找个穿夜总会礼服的金发助理律师不也是要让我忌妒吗?
Oh,and Paralegally Blonde isn't here in her low-cut dress to make me jealous?
哦，那么你是说她是妓女?
Oh,so now she's a whore?
什么?
What?
你知道吗?助理律师Mary很棒
You know something? Mary the paralegal is awesome.
你要知道 我今天来不是要让你忌妒
And you know what else? I didn't come here tonight to make you jealous,
而是要像一个朋友那样支持你
I came here to support you as a friend.
而老实说 我已经厌倦了这种尝试了
And frankly,I'm sick of trying.
我喜欢那人
I like that guy.
- 嘿 \n- 嘿
- Hey. \n- Hey.
你们在那谈什么?
What were you guys talking about over there?
哦，我只是告诉我朋友 我觉得你很棒
Oh,I was,uh,just telling my friend that I think you're awesome.
嗯，谢谢
Well,thanks.
你知道吗 这是我进过的最好的酒店
You know,this is one of the nicer hotels I've ever been in.
哦 我的朋友负责改造过这
Oh,yeah,my friend did the remodel.
你应该看看这的客房 风景很漂亮
You should see the rooms. The views are amazing.
是吗 也许我们没有房间太糟了
Yeah? Maybe it's too bad we don't have a room.
1506房 我付钱 你们去疯吧
Room 1506. My treat. You kids go nuts.
事实上，不要用迷你条
Actually,don't use the mini-bar.
去吧 拜托 Ted 去吧
Do it. Come on,Ted,do it.
这是你30岁之前必须做的一件事
This is one of those things you have to do before you turn 30.
和妓女上床？
Sleep with a prostitute?
不 告别处男身
No,lose your virginity. What up.
统计证明 和妓女至少一次有染的男人在今后的恋情中成功的几率
Statistic-- men who have had at least one relationship with a prostitute
至少要高出75％
are 75% more likely to have success in future relationships.
你编的
You just made that up.
- 撤销 \n- 律师
- Withdrawn. \n- Lawyered.
好吧 有三点 一 Robin的奖就要颁了
Okay,three things. First of all,Robin's category's almost up.
二 你不该这么做
And second of all,you cannot do this.
不论怎么说这都是错的
It's wrong on every level.
三 我偷偷弄了点小东西在Sandy的头发上 \n他还没有发现
And third,I've been placing small items in Sandy's hair all night. He still hasn't noticed.
我知道我不能这么做 我不会做的
I know I can't do this. I'm not doing this.
只是有点可惜
It's just...it's a shame.
她很酷
She's really cool.
对了，嗯...开始了
Yeah,well... there we go.
一辆单车-- 兜风还是危险?
A Bicycle-- Joyride or Deathtrap?
Mike Murphy 13岁怀孕和吸毒
Mike Murphy for 13, Pregnant and Addicted.
Robin Scherbotsky的小菜，歌唱的狗狗
And Robin Scherbotsky for Pickles,the Singing Dog.
获奖者是...
And the winner is...
Robin Scherbotsky\nRobin Scherbotsky.
多谢
Thanks.
哦，哇，这真是个惊喜
Oh,wow. This is really a surprise.
嗯，你知道和我的朋友们一起分享这个奖棒极了
Um,you know it's nice to be able to share this award with my friends.
他们今天都来了
They're all here tonight.
Marshall,Lily,Sandy Rivers...\nMarshall,Lily,Sandy Rivers...
Barney...\nBarney...
就这些 他们是我所有的朋友
And that's it. Those are all my friends.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 恭喜 \n- 哦，谢谢
- Congratulations. \n- Oh,thanks.
嗯，Sandy想叫辆出租车吗?
Um,Sandy,do you want to get a cab?
好 我们走
Sure. Let's go.
对 这个派对已经完了 Mary你想上楼去吗?
Yeah,this party's dead. Mary,you want to go upstairs?
我们，嗯……有个房间
We,uh,got a room.
伙计 你在干什么?
Dude,what are you doing?
看起来是什么?
What's it look like?
看起来很遭，你不能这么做
It looks bad,is what it looks like. You cannot do this.
Marshall,如果了解她你就知道 她真的是个很酷的女孩
Marshall,she is a really cool girl when you get to know her.
而且我想让Robin忌妒
Besides,I'm trying to make Robin jealous.
哦 那太成熟了
Oh,that's real mature.
Marshall,Marshell你和Ted在说什么?
Marshall,what is up with you and Ted?
没事宝贝，别担心
Nothing,baby. Don't worry about it.
好，做你想做的事吧
Fine. Do what you want.
嘿
Hey.
我们走吗?
Should we go?
好
Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗯...
Well...
晚安
Good night.
那么，你和Barney有没有...?
So,did you and Barney ever...?
世上可没有足够的钱
There's not enough money in the world.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh,thank God.
哇 那么说他们...?
Wow,so they're...?
Robin，Sandy Rivers在哪?
Robin,where's Sandy Rivers?
我送他上了出租车
I put him in a cab.
那么你和他不是...?
So you and he aren't...?
我不和同事约会
I don't date people I work with.
我只是想让Ted忌妒
I was just trying to make Ted jealous.
他呢...?
Is he...?
他也是想让你忌妒
He's off trying to make you jealous.
哦，嗯，他们不错啊
Oh,well,good for them.
而且，你知道吗，如果Ted喜欢她 她也许真的很酷
And,you know,if Ted likes her,she's probably pretty cool.
Lily我知道你在睡觉
Lily,I know you're asleep,
但我必须告诉某个人 我们不向对方隐瞒任何事情 \n所以 我要说了
but I have to tell someone this,and we tell each other everything. So,here it goes.
Mary不是助理律师
Mary's not a paralegal.
她是妓女
She's a prostitute.
Mary是妓女?
Mary's a prostitute?
什么?!
What?!
Barney付的钱
Barney paid for her.
真的吗?
Is that true?
我们谈了关于嫖妓的事
We were having a conversation about prostitution,
然后Barney打了电话给她 她就出现在酒吧了
and then Barney calls her up and then she shows up at the bar
而现在她和Ted在楼上了
and now she and Ted are upstairs.
哦 说真的 Ted最近到底是怎么回事?
Okay,seriously,what is going on with Ted lately?
他精神出问题了吗?
Is he having a nervous breakdown?
你知道吗 Barney 对任何人来说这都是更深的新堕落
You know,Barney,for anyone else,this would be a new low,
但对你来说只是新的中度堕落
but sadly,for you,it's just a new middle.
哦 我的天 我用了她的唇膏 ! 噢!
Oh,my God,I used her lipstick! Ah!
那是她的餐巾
That's her napkin.
不!
No!
好，嗯，我想现在是最好的时机了
Okay,well,I guess now is as good a time as any.
为了保持今晚的颁奖主题
In keeping with tonight's award show motif,
我想宣布本晚最曲折的结局!
I'd like to announce this evening's big twist ending!
吸血鬼Lou,有幸请你宣布吗?
Vampire Lou,would you do the honors?
"Mary不是真妓女"
"Mary's not really a prostitute."
什么?
What?
就这样吸血鬼Lou. 干得好
That's all,Vampire Lou. Nicely done.
- 那么她不是...? \n- 对
- So she's not...?  \n- No.
Mary只是住在我那幢楼里的一个助理律师
Mary's just a paralegal who lives in my building.
哦-- 哈-哈!而且最有趣的是--
Oh-- ha-ha! And here's the best part--
她不知道Ted以为她是妓女
she has no idea that Ted thinks she's a hooker.
哦 拜托
Oh,come on.
如果你们不笑 就好像太吝啬了
If you don't laugh,it just seems mean.
我觉得自己是里查・基尔
I feel kind of like Richard Gere.
- 不是对自己的样子害羞，对吗? \n- 对
- Not shy about your looks,are you? \n- No.
你知道吗，Mary，我从来没这么做过
You know,Mary,I've never done this before.
做什么?
Done what?
你知道，“约会”
You know,been... on a "date."
是的，对
Yeah,right.
等等，你是在开玩笑，对吗
Wait,you're kidding,right?
不
No.
怎么 这很奇怪吗?
Why,is that so odd?
嗯，Ted，我的意思是，我15岁就开始和人约会了
Well,Ted,I mean,I've been going on dates since I was 15.
天 你那时候还是个孩子啊
God,you were just a kid.
嗯，瞧，我们先喝点酒 这样我们就能放松
Well,look,let's just have a few drinks. We'll relax and...
好 听起来不错 我的客户整天骑在我身上
Yeah,that sounds great. I had clients riding me all day long.
一定很难
Must be tough.
对，我是说我有个客户就是不能放过我
Yeah. I mean,this one guy just wouldn't leave me alone.
我的意思是，和我讨论肛门
I mean,talk about anal.
嗯，我们到了
Well,here we are.
好吧 Mary 我很喜欢你
Okay,look,Mary,I like you a lot.
我这么喜欢你都让我有点吃惊了，但我不能这么做
I'm sort of amazed at how much I like you,but I can't do this.
你是个妓女
You're a hooker.
什么?
What?
瞧，也许我太老土 但是对不起 这是违背我的原则的
Look,maybe I'm old-fashioned,but I'm sorry,that's a deal-breaker for me.
我不会和妓女上床
I'm not going to have sex with a prostitute.
不... Ted 我是个助理律师
No... Ted,I'm a paralegal.
拜托Mary,这里也没有别人
Come on,Mary,there's no one else around.
你是个妓女
You're a hooker.
不 Ted ...
No,Ted...
我是个助理律师
I'm a paralegal.
不 你是个妓女
No,you're a hooker.
不 我是个助理律师
No,I'm a paralegal.
你是个助理律师
You're a paralegal.
这不好笑
That was not funny.
不好笑 伙计
Not funny,dude.
我知道，这是场闹剧
I know,it was hilarious.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
我想证实一点
I did it to prove a point.
证实什么?
What point?
别走开，我就想到了
Stay with me. It's going to come to me.
哦 好 我要证实的是
Ah,okay,here's the point.
你确定了Mary的身份 对吗?
You thought that Mary was a sure thing,right?
然后发生了什么? 第一次约会她就带你去了酒店房间
So what happened? She took you up to a hotel room on the first date.
你要做的就是对每个女人都这样
All you have to do is be that confident with every girl you meet
你的阳痿就解决了
and your slump is over.
你要传达的讯息就是我要像对待妓女一样对待每个女人?
So the message is,I should treat every woman like a whore?
拜托 伙计 你不应该感谢我吗
Come on,dude,you should be thanking me.
她打了我一个耳光，怒气冲冲的走了
She slapped me and stormed off.
你能怪她吗? 你叫人家妓女
Can you blame her? You called her a hooker.
对不起 伙计 这挺好笑
I'm sorry,dude,it was funny.
对 嗯 已经晚了 我要回我的房间了
Yeah. Well,it's getting late. I should get back to my room.
你的房间?
Your room?
对 那间非常贵的酒店房间是你用信用卡付款的--
Yeah,that really expensive hotel room you put on your credit card--
还没退房
never checked out.
顺便说下 你知道什么超级有趣吗?
By the way,you know what's super fun?
我要把Dom Perignon倒进下水道(Dom Perignon是一种昂贵的法国香槟)
Pouring Dom Perignon down a bathtub drain.
嗯  快三点了 我要按摩一下
Well,it's almost 3:00. Got a massage. Toodles.
拜托 如果你不笑，那你好像太吝啬了
Come on,if you don't laugh,it just seems mean.